anifreak.com 2016-11-22

# aniFreak > Your #1 Anime and Manga Resource! > Main > Privacy

## Privacy Policy

**All privacy-related information can be found below.  
** This privacy policy was last updated on 2013-06-29. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, they will immediately be posted on this page of our website. 

**We collect personal and activity data, which may be linked.  
** We use technologies like cookies (small files stored on your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address.

We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name or email address. If authorized by you, we may also access profile and other information from services like Facebook.

Our systems may associate this personal information with your activities in the course of providing service to you (such as pages you view or things you click on or search for).

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information. 

**We do not store or share your precise location.** We do not use or collect your precise geographic location. 

**You can request to see your personal data.** You can sign into your account to see any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name and email address. You can also contact us by email to request to see this information. 

**We may keep data indefinitely.  
** We may keep data indefinitely. 

**We may share personal data with companies we trust.** We may share personally identifiable information (such as name and email address) with trusted partners in order to provide you with relevant advertising, offers or services.

California residents are legally entitled (at no charge and no more than once annually) to request information about how we may have shared your information with others for direct marketing purposes. Contact us for this information:

admin@anifreak.com 

**Ad companies collect anonymous data. You can opt out.  
** Ad companies may use and collect anonymous data about your interests to customize content and advertising here and in other sites and applications. Interest and location data may be linked to your device, but is not linked to your identity. Click to see company privacy policies and opt-out choices: 

Google's mission is to organize the world's information and make it universally accessible and useful.   

**You can ask privacy questions.  
** If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us:

admin@anifreak.com 

**Analytics providers access data on our behalf.  
** Analytics companies may access anonymous data (such as your IP address or device ID) to help us understand how our services are used. They use this data solely on our behalf. They do not share it except in aggregate form; no data is shared as to any individual user. Click to see company privacy policies that govern their use of data. 

Google Analytics is a web analytics tool that helps website owners understand how visitors engage with their website. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve it. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors.   

**We take steps to protect personal information  
** We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. We encrypt transmission of data on pages where you provide payment information. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error.

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. 

**Special situations may require disclosure of your data.  
** To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so.
